<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/"><category term="multi" label="r/multi"/><updated>2021-03-26T16:26:15+00:00</updated><id>/r/pennystocks+investing+wallstreetbets2+stocks/.rss</id><link rel="self" href="https://www.reddit.com/r/pennystocks+investing+wallstreetbets2+stocks/.rss" type="application/atom+xml" /><link rel="alternate" href="https://www.reddit.com/r/pennystocks+investing+wallstreetbets2+stocks/" type="text/html" /><title>posts from investing, stocks, pennystocks, wallstreetbets2</title><entry><author><name>/u/juaggo_</name><uri>https://www.reddit.com/user/juaggo_</uri></author><category term="stocks" label="r/stocks"/><content type="html">&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;So lately the market has been going down and people might have gotten some bloody days in their portfolios. The correction has affected tech the most as the Nasdaq is about 8% from its all time highs.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;The correction has happened because of number one: Rising treasury yields and number two: Sector rotation. Reopening plays are currently the trend that big money likes and money has gone there recently. &lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;This doesn’t mean that tech is bad in the long term. Stocks go down sometimes and this is the moment that it’s happening. But there is a silver lining to this story...&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;This gives us a good opportunity get your favourite stocks at a cheaper price. Averaging down is a very delightful thing to do and this is a perfect opportunity. And even if we continue to go down, it’s ok, since you can average down even more.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Another thing that I want to say is that you shouldn’t listen to the media too much. It’s their job to create havoc and drama in the stock market. Their opinions change every week almost, and it’s kinda funny sometimes. One week they say that you shouldn’t sell and another day CNBC reporters tell us how big tech is in a bad place and you should move to industrials, travel, etc. &lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;You have YOUR own plan. Do your plan and don’t listen to those whose job is to dramatize things. The stock market needs patience. Investing is for the long run.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Don’t look at the 1 day chart all the time. It can be very toxic for yourself, especially during a red day. So just chill and remember that your time horizon is in 10 years, not tomorrow.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;That’s my 2 cents, have good one everyone!&lt;/p&gt; &lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt; &amp;#32; submitted by &amp;#32; &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.reddit.com/user/juaggo_&quot;&gt; /u/juaggo_ &lt;/a&gt; &amp;#32; to &amp;#32; &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.reddit.com/r/stocks/&quot;&gt; r/stocks &lt;/a&gt; &lt;br/&gt; &lt;span&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.reddit.com/r/stocks/comments/mdn3nz/tech_is_tanking_at_the_moment_but_it_will_come/&quot;&gt;[link]&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &amp;#32; &lt;span&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.reddit.com/r/stocks/comments/mdn3nz/tech_is_tanking_at_the_moment_but_it_will_come/&quot;&gt;[comments]&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;</content><id>t3_mdn3nz</id><link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/stocks/comments/mdn3nz/tech_is_tanking_at_the_moment_but_it_will_come/" /><updated>2021-03-26T12:04:26+00:00</updated><title>Tech is tanking at the moment, but it will come back up eventually. Don’t listen to the big media platforms too much!</title></entry><entry><author><name>/u/vanchman11</name><uri>https://www.reddit.com/user/vanchman11</uri></author><category term="investing" label="r/investing"/><content type="html">&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.cnbc.com/2021/03/26/sofi-to-give-amateur-investors-early-access-to-ipos-in-break-from-wall-street-tradition-.html&quot;&gt;https://www.cnbc.com/2021/03/26/sofi-to-give-amateur-investors-early-access-to-ipos-in-break-from-wall-street-tradition-.html&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Online finance start-up SoFi is lowering the barrier for amateur investors to buy shares of companies as they go public.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;These IPO shares have historically been set aside for Wall Street&amp;#39;s institutional investors or high-net worth individuals. Retail traders don&amp;#39;t have a way to buy into newly listed companies until those shares begin actually trading on the exchange. By that time, the price has often gapped higher.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&amp;quot;Main Street will have access to investing in a way they wouldn&amp;#39;t have before,&amp;quot; SoFi CEO Anthony Noto said in a phone interview. &amp;quot;It gives more differentiation, and more access so people can build diversified portfolios.&amp;quot;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;SoFi itself will be an underwriter in these deals, meaning it works with companies to determine a share price, buys securities from the issuer then sells them back to certain investors. It&amp;#39;s common for brokerage firms to get a portion of IPO shares in that process. But they don&amp;#39;t typically offer them to the everyday investor.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Noto worked on more than 50 IPOs, including Twitter&amp;#39;s debut, in his former role as partner and head of the technology media and telecom group at Goldman Sachs. Firms like Goldman generate revenue from Wall Street funds, which often choose to get in on an IPO &amp;quot;based on the access they get to that unique product,&amp;quot; he said.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&amp;quot;Individual investors don&amp;#39;t generate those types of revenues, therefore they don&amp;#39;t get access to the unique product,&amp;quot; Noto said. &amp;quot;The cost of serving retail, if they did decide to do that, would be too high.&amp;quot;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;SoFi clients who have at least $3,000 in account value will be able enter the amount of shares they want as a &amp;quot;reservation.&amp;quot; The app will alert them when it&amp;#39;s time to confirm an order.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt; &amp;#32; submitted by &amp;#32; &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.reddit.com/user/vanchman11&quot;&gt; /u/vanchman11 &lt;/a&gt; &amp;#32; to &amp;#32; &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.reddit.com/r/investing/&quot;&gt; r/investing &lt;/a&gt; &lt;br/&gt; &lt;span&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.reddit.com/r/investing/comments/mdppti/sofi_to_give_amateur_investors_early_access_to/&quot;&gt;[link]&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &amp;#32; &lt;span&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.reddit.com/r/investing/comments/mdppti/sofi_to_give_amateur_investors_early_access_to/&quot;&gt;[comments]&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;</content><id>t3_mdppti</id><link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/investing/comments/mdppti/sofi_to_give_amateur_investors_early_access_to/" /><updated>2021-03-26T14:20:52+00:00</updated><title>SoFi to give amateur investors early access to IPOs</title></entry><entry><author><name>/u/Muznick</name><uri>https://www.reddit.com/user/Muznick</uri></author><category term="pennystocks" label="r/pennystocks"/><content type="html">&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Another day another store opened! &lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;CALGARY, AB, March 26, 2021 /CNW/ - High Tide Inc. (&amp;quot;High Tide&amp;quot; or the &amp;quot;Company&amp;quot;) (TSXV: $HITI) (OTCQB: $HITIF) (FRA: $2LY), a retail-focused cannabis corporation enhanced by the manufacturing and distribution of consumption accessories, announced today that its new Canna Cabana retail store, located at 3505 Upper Middle Road, Unit D3, in Burlington, Ontario, has begun selling recreational cannabis products for adult use. The new store represents High Tide&amp;#39;s 80th branded retail location across Canada selling recreational cannabis products and consumption accessories, and the Company&amp;#39;s eighth new organically built store in the month of March alone. The new Burlington store is strategically located within a popular commercial plaza with a major grocery anchor and several national restaurant chains nearby.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&amp;quot;The new store is another step towards our commitment of reaching 30 branded retail locations within Ontario by September of this year. I am so proud of the work our team has put into launching eight new stores this month alone. March has been the busiest month in terms of new store openings since High Tide&amp;#39;s inception,&amp;quot; said Raj Grover, President and Chief Executive Officer of High Tide. &amp;quot;Continued expansion in Canada&amp;#39;s largest province remains a core part of High Tide&amp;#39;s organic growth strategy. We will continue to execute this strategy by bringing our one-stop cannabis shop concept to high traffic areas like the new Upper Middle Store in Burlington,&amp;quot; added Mr. Grover.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;About High Tide Inc.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;High Tide is a retail-focused cannabis company enhanced by the manufacturing and distribution of consumption accessories. The Company is the largest Canadian retailer of recreational cannabis as measured by revenue, with 80 branded retail locations spanning Ontario, Alberta, Manitoba and Saskatchewan. High Tide&amp;#39;s retail segment features the Canna Cabana, KushBar, Meta Cannabis Co., Meta Cannabis Supply Co. and NewLeaf Cannabis banners, with additional locations under development across the country. High Tide has been serving consumers for over a decade through its numerous consumption accessory businesses including e-commerce platforms Grasscity.com, Smokecartel.com and CBDcity.com, and its wholesale distribution division under Valiant Distribution, including the licensed entertainment product manufacturer Famous Brandz. High Tide&amp;#39;s strategy as a parent company is to extend and strengthen its integrated value chain, while providing a complete customer experience and maximizing shareholder value. Key industry investors in High Tide include Aphria Inc. (TSX: $APHA) (NYSE: $APHA) and Aurora Cannabis Inc. (NYSE: $ACB) (TSX: $ACB).&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Neither the TSX Venture Exchange (the &amp;quot;TSXV&amp;quot;) nor its Regulation Services Provider (as that term is defined in the policies of the TSXV) accepts responsibility for the adequacy or accuracy of this release.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt; &amp;#32; submitted by &amp;#32; &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.reddit.com/user/Muznick&quot;&gt; /u/Muznick &lt;/a&gt; &amp;#32; to &amp;#32; &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.reddit.com/r/pennystocks/&quot;&gt; r/pennystocks &lt;/a&gt; &lt;br/&gt; &lt;span&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.reddit.com/r/pennystocks/comments/mdlyq8/guess_what_high_tide_opened_a_new_store/&quot;&gt;[link]&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &amp;#32; &lt;span&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.reddit.com/r/pennystocks/comments/mdlyq8/guess_what_high_tide_opened_a_new_store/&quot;&gt;[comments]&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;</content><id>t3_mdlyq8</id><link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/pennystocks/comments/mdlyq8/guess_what_high_tide_opened_a_new_store/" /><updated>2021-03-26T10:51:46+00:00</updated><title>Guess what, $HITI opened a new store.</title></entry><entry><author><name>/u/TobiasKGordon</name><uri>https://www.reddit.com/user/TobiasKGordon</uri></author><category term="wallstreetbets2" label="r/wallstreetbets2"/><content type="html">&amp;#32; submitted by &amp;#32; &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.reddit.com/user/TobiasKGordon&quot;&gt; /u/TobiasKGordon &lt;/a&gt; &amp;#32; to &amp;#32; &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.reddit.com/r/wallstreetbets2/&quot;&gt; r/wallstreetbets2 &lt;/a&gt; &lt;br/&gt; &lt;span&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://i.redd.it/y6cvhu4uk8p61.jpg&quot;&gt;[link]&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &amp;#32; &lt;span&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.reddit.com/r/wallstreetbets2/comments/md7zya/gme_to_the_moon/&quot;&gt;[comments]&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;</content><id>t3_md7zya</id><link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/wallstreetbets2/comments/md7zya/gme_to_the_moon/" /><updated>2021-03-25T20:46:30+00:00</updated><title>$GME to the Moon!</title></entry><entry><author><name>/u/DangerStranger138</name><uri>https://www.reddit.com/user/DangerStranger138</uri></author><category term="wallstreetbets2" label="r/wallstreetbets2"/><content type="html">&amp;#32; submitted by &amp;#32; &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.reddit.com/user/DangerStranger138&quot;&gt; /u/DangerStranger138 &lt;/a&gt; &amp;#32; to &amp;#32; &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.reddit.com/r/wallstreetbets2/&quot;&gt; r/wallstreetbets2 &lt;/a&gt; &lt;br/&gt; &lt;span&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://markets.businessinsider.com/news/stocks/mormon-church-fund-sells-big-tech-buys-tesla-gamestop-stock-2021-3-1030242012&quot;&gt;[link]&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &amp;#32; &lt;span&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.reddit.com/r/wallstreetbets2/comments/mdhn4z/mormons_love_the_stocks/&quot;&gt;[comments]&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;</content><id>t3_mdhn4z</id><link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/wallstreetbets2/comments/mdhn4z/mormons_love_the_stocks/" /><updated>2021-03-26T05:34:38+00:00</updated><title>Mormons love the stocks $GME</title></entry><entry><author><name>/u/coolcomfort123</name><uri>https://www.reddit.com/user/coolcomfort123</uri></author><category term="stocks" label="r/stocks"/><content type="html">&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.cnbc.com/2021/03/09/microsoft-closes-bethesda-acquisition-aiming-to-take-on-sony.html&quot;&gt;https://www.cnbc.com/2021/03/09/microsoft-closes-bethesda-acquisition-aiming-to-take-on-sony.html&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;$MSFT has closed its $7.5 billion acquisition of ZeniMax, the parent company of Bethesda.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Microsoft confirmed that some new Bethesda games would be exclusive to Xbox consoles and PCs.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;The firm has often been seen as lagging behind Sony when it comes to major first-party releases.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;This is a positive news as msft could improve the gaming business. It will be more competitive to sony and able to generate more subscription revenue. The stock is trading around $230 and it is an attractive entry point for long term investors.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt; &amp;#32; submitted by &amp;#32; &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.reddit.com/user/coolcomfort123&quot;&gt; /u/coolcomfort123 &lt;/a&gt; &amp;#32; to &amp;#32; &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.reddit.com/r/stocks/&quot;&gt; r/stocks &lt;/a&gt; &lt;br/&gt; &lt;span&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.reddit.com/r/stocks/comments/mdnzup/microsoft_closes_75_billion_bethesda_acquisition/&quot;&gt;[link]&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &amp;#32; &lt;span&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.reddit.com/r/stocks/comments/mdnzup/microsoft_closes_75_billion_bethesda_acquisition/&quot;&gt;[comments]&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;</content><id>t3_mdnzup</id><link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/stocks/comments/mdnzup/microsoft_closes_75_billion_bethesda_acquisition/" /><updated>2021-03-26T12:55:18+00:00</updated><title>$MSFT closes $7.5 billion Bethesda acquisition, aiming to take on Sony with exclusive games</title></entry><entry><author><name>/u/TheSubwayTrader</name><uri>https://www.reddit.com/user/TheSubwayTrader</uri></author><category term="wallstreetbets2" label="r/wallstreetbets2"/><content type="html">&amp;#32; submitted by &amp;#32; &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.reddit.com/user/TheSubwayTrader&quot;&gt; /u/TheSubwayTrader &lt;/a&gt; &amp;#32; to &amp;#32; &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.reddit.com/r/wallstreetbets2/&quot;&gt; r/wallstreetbets2 &lt;/a&gt; &lt;br/&gt; &lt;span&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://i.redd.it/ml6fd7gam6p61.gif&quot;&gt;[link]&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &amp;#32; &lt;span&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.reddit.com/r/wallstreetbets2/comments/mcz3z9/amc_10_9_8_7_6_5_4_3_2_1/&quot;&gt;[comments]&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;</content><id>t3_mcz3z9</id><link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/wallstreetbets2/comments/mcz3z9/amc_10_9_8_7_6_5_4_3_2_1/" /><updated>2021-03-25T14:09:57+00:00</updated><title>AMC 10, 9, 8, 7, 6, 5, 4, 3, 2, 1</title></entry><entry><author><name>/u/Hichek2</name><uri>https://www.reddit.com/user/Hichek2</uri></author><category term="investing" label="r/investing"/><content type="html">&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.cnbc.com/2021/03/25/fed-says-banks-will-have-to-wait-until-june-30-to-start-issuing-buybacks-and-bigger-dividends.html&quot;&gt;https://www.cnbc.com/2021/03/25/fed-says-banks-will-have-to-wait-until-june-30-to-start-issuing-buybacks-and-bigger-dividends.html&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Fed says banks will have to wait until June 30 to start issuing buybacks and bigger dividends&lt;/p&gt; &lt;ul&gt; &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Big banks will be allowed to resume normal levels of dividend payouts and share repurchases as of June 30, as long as they pass this year’s stress test.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Payouts had been restricted based on income, as a precautionary move during the Covid-19 pandemic.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Banks that fail the stress test will have to wait until Sept. 30, and face even more stringent measures if they still don’t meet capital requirements by then.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/li&gt; &lt;/ul&gt; &lt;p&gt;Banks will be able to accelerate dividends and buybacks to shareholders this year, but not until June 30 and provided they pass the current round of stress tests, the Federal Reserve announced on Thursday.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;The biggest Wall Street institutions have been limited based on income in their ability to do both for nearly the past year as a precautionary measure during &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.cnbc.com/2021/03/25/covid-live-updates.html&quot;&gt;the Covid-19 pandemic&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;The Fed had said late last year that it would begin allowing regular disbursements in the first quarter of 2021, so the Thursday announcement pushes that date back.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;ADVERTISING&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;“The banking system continues to be a source of strength and returning to our normal framework after this year’s stress test will preserve that strength,” Vice Chair for Supervision Randal Quarles said in a statement.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Bank stocks rose in after-hours trading on the news, with Wells Fargo and $JPM up around 1%.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Lifting the restrictions only applies to institutions that maintain proper capital levels as evaluated through the stress tests. Under normal circumstances, capital distributions are guided by a bank’s “stress capital buffer,” a measure of capital that each bank should carry based on the riskiness of its holdings.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;The income-based measures &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.cnbc.com/2020/12/18/fed-to-allow-big-banks-to-resume-share-buybacks-with-limitations.html&quot;&gt;were put in place&lt;/a&gt; as a safeguard to make sure banks had enough capital as the pandemic tore through the U.S. economy.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Any bank not reaching the target will have the pandemic-era restrictions reimposed until Sept. 30. Banks that still can’t meet the required capital levels will face even stricter limitations.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;The financial sector is one of the stock market’s leaders this year, with the group up 14.7% year to date on the S&amp;amp;P 500. People’s United, Fifth Third and Wells Fargo have led the banking space.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;The announcement comes a day after Treasury Secretary Janet Yellen, who chaired the Fed from 2014-18, said &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.cnbc.com/2021/03/24/yellen-supports-buybacks-warren-wants-blackrock-deemed-too-big-to-fail.html&quot;&gt;she would be comfortable&lt;/a&gt; with lifting the restrictions on dividends and buybacks.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;At a congressional hearing Wednesday, Yellen said she agreed both with the decision to suspend capital disbursements, and to resume them.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;“I have been opposed earlier when we were very concerned about the situation the banks would face about stock buybacks,” Yellen said. “But financial institutions look healthier now, and I believe they should have some of the liberty provided by the rules to make returns to shareholders.”&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Banks bought back just $80.7 billion of their shares in 2020, with most coming before the pandemic hit.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt; &amp;#32; submitted by &amp;#32; &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.reddit.com/user/Hichek2&quot;&gt; /u/Hichek2 &lt;/a&gt; &amp;#32; to &amp;#32; &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.reddit.com/r/investing/&quot;&gt; r/investing &lt;/a&gt; &lt;br/&gt; &lt;span&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.reddit.com/r/investing/comments/md937s/fed_says_banks_will_have_to_wait_until_june_30_to/&quot;&gt;[link]&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &amp;#32; &lt;span&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.reddit.com/r/investing/comments/md937s/fed_says_banks_will_have_to_wait_until_june_30_to/&quot;&gt;[comments]&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;</content><id>t3_md937s</id><link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/investing/comments/md937s/fed_says_banks_will_have_to_wait_until_june_30_to/" /><updated>2021-03-25T21:37:04+00:00</updated><title>Fed says banks will have to wait until June 30 to start issuing buybacks and bigger dividends</title></entry><entry><author><name>/u/TheSubwayTrader</name><uri>https://www.reddit.com/user/TheSubwayTrader</uri></author><category term="wallstreetbets2" label="r/wallstreetbets2"/><content type="html">&amp;#32; submitted by &amp;#32; &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.reddit.com/user/TheSubwayTrader&quot;&gt; /u/TheSubwayTrader &lt;/a&gt; &amp;#32; to &amp;#32; &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.reddit.com/r/wallstreetbets2/&quot;&gt; r/wallstreetbets2 &lt;/a&gt; &lt;br/&gt; &lt;span&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://i.redd.it/cx9w20i3l7p61.gif&quot;&gt;[link]&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &amp;#32; &lt;span&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.reddit.com/r/wallstreetbets2/comments/md3jio/gme_roller_coaster_of_love/&quot;&gt;[comments]&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;</content><id>t3_md3jio</id><link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/wallstreetbets2/comments/md3jio/gme_roller_coaster_of_love/" /><updated>2021-03-25T17:25:17+00:00</updated><title>GME Roller Coaster of Love</title></entry><entry><author><name>/u/TheSubwayTrader</name><uri>https://www.reddit.com/user/TheSubwayTrader</uri></author><category term="wallstreetbets2" label="r/wallstreetbets2"/><content type="html">&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;EL CAJON, CA / ACCESSWIRE / March 25, 2021 /&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href=&quot;https://pr.report/DoRzBe1j&quot;&gt;Solar Integrated Roofing Corp.&lt;/a&gt; (OTC Pink:&lt;a href=&quot;https://marketwirenews.com/stock/sirc/&quot;&gt;SIRC&lt;/a&gt;), an integrated, single-source solar power and roofing systems installation company, today provided a corporate update on near-term operational and capital markets milestone achievements.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&amp;quot;As we transition into a national brand with various portfolio companies across the country, we will seek to uplist to the $OTCQB in the near-term with a goal of uplisting to Nasdaq thereafter,&amp;quot; said David Massey, Chief Executive Officer of Solar Integrated Roofing Corp. &amp;quot;This marks a new era for our shareholders as we continue to mature and improve our prestige within the capital markets community.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://marketwirenews.com/news-releases/isw-holdings-to-take-center-stage-at-prestigious-min-5665692495868452.html&quot;&gt;https://marketwirenews.com/news-releases/isw-holdings-to-take-center-stage-at-prestigious-min-5665692495868452.html&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&amp;#x200B;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;#parler #stocks #pennystocks&lt;/p&gt; &lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt; &amp;#32; submitted by &amp;#32; &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.reddit.com/user/TheSubwayTrader&quot;&gt; /u/TheSubwayTrader &lt;/a&gt; &amp;#32; to &amp;#32; &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.reddit.com/r/wallstreetbets2/&quot;&gt; r/wallstreetbets2 &lt;/a&gt; &lt;br/&gt; &lt;span&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.reddit.com/r/wallstreetbets2/comments/mdny9i/iswh_takes_center_stage_at_crypto_conference/&quot;&gt;[link]&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &amp;#32; &lt;span&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.reddit.com/r/wallstreetbets2/comments/mdny9i/iswh_takes_center_stage_at_crypto_conference/&quot;&gt;[comments]&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;</content><id>t3_mdny9i</id><link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/wallstreetbets2/comments/mdny9i/iswh_takes_center_stage_at_crypto_conference/" /><updated>2021-03-26T12:53:01+00:00</updated><title>$ISWH Takes Center Stage at Crypto Conference 'Mining Disrupt'</title></entry><entry><author><name>/u/AutoModerator</name><uri>https://www.reddit.com/user/AutoModerator</uri></author><category term="wallstreetbets2" label="r/wallstreetbets2"/><content type="html">&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Buy? Sell? Call? Put? Iron triangle? Steel curtain? MEAT CURTAIN? You tell us&lt;/p&gt; &lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt; &amp;#32; submitted by &amp;#32; &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.reddit.com/user/AutoModerator&quot;&gt; /u/AutoModerator &lt;/a&gt; &amp;#32; to &amp;#32; &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.reddit.com/r/wallstreetbets2/&quot;&gt; r/wallstreetbets2 &lt;/a&gt; &lt;br/&gt; &lt;span&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.reddit.com/r/wallstreetbets2/comments/mdkfns/daily_plays_positions_and_problems_thread/&quot;&gt;[link]&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &amp;#32; &lt;span&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.reddit.com/r/wallstreetbets2/comments/mdkfns/daily_plays_positions_and_problems_thread/&quot;&gt;[comments]&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;</content><id>t3_mdkfns</id><link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/wallstreetbets2/comments/mdkfns/daily_plays_positions_and_problems_thread/" /><updated>2021-03-26T09:00:18+00:00</updated><title>Daily Plays, Positions, and Problems Thread!</title></entry><entry><author><name>/u/dufusoftheriver</name><uri>https://www.reddit.com/user/dufusoftheriver</uri></author><category term="pennystocks" label="r/pennystocks"/><content type="html">&lt;table&gt; &lt;tr&gt;&lt;td&gt; &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.reddit.com/r/pennystocks/comments/mcx9l9/some_weirdo_tried_to_sell_me_something_he/&quot;&gt; &lt;img src=&quot;https://a.thumbs.redditmedia.com/y6h3vi6WRca5QI0scXWgTZiIDq6XBzhuTy90rpWDCC4.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Some weirdo tried to sell me something, he messaged me after I commented on a thread here.&quot; title=&quot;Some weirdo tried to sell me something, he messaged me after I commented on a thread here.&quot; /&gt; &lt;/a&gt; &lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt; &amp;#32; submitted by &amp;#32; &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.reddit.com/user/dufusoftheriver&quot;&gt; /u/dufusoftheriver &lt;/a&gt; &amp;#32; to &amp;#32; &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.reddit.com/r/pennystocks/&quot;&gt; r/pennystocks &lt;/a&gt; &lt;br/&gt; &lt;span&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.reddit.com/gallery/mcx9l9&quot;&gt;[link]&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &amp;#32; &lt;span&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.reddit.com/r/pennystocks/comments/mcx9l9/some_weirdo_tried_to_sell_me_something_he/&quot;&gt;[comments]&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;&lt;/table&gt;</content><id>t3_mcx9l9</id><media:thumbnail url="https://a.thumbs.redditmedia.com/y6h3vi6WRca5QI0scXWgTZiIDq6XBzhuTy90rpWDCC4.jpg" /><link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/pennystocks/comments/mcx9l9/some_weirdo_tried_to_sell_me_something_he/" /><updated>2021-03-25T12:38:57+00:00</updated><title>Some weirdo tried to sell me something, he messaged me after I commented on a thread here.</title></entry><entry><author><name>/u/TowerTom</name><uri>https://www.reddit.com/user/TowerTom</uri></author><category term="pennystocks" label="r/pennystocks"/><content type="html">&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;Https://www.proactiveinvestors.co.uk/companies/news/944988/argo-blockchain-enters-partnership-to-launch-first-clean-energy-bitcoin-mining-pool-944988.html&quot;&gt;Https://www.proactiveinvestors.co.uk/companies/news/944988/argo-blockchain-enters-partnership-to-launch-first-clean-energy-bitcoin-mining-pool-944988.html&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&amp;quot;Argo Blockchain PLC (LON: $ARB) (OTCQX: $ARBKF) said it has signed a memorandum of understanding (MOU) with DMG Blockchain Solutions, a blockchain and cryptocurrency technology firm, to launch the first Bitcoin mining pool powered exclusively by clean energy.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Under the terms of the deal, Argo and DMG will jointly launch Terra Pool, which will initially consist of both companies processing power which is mostly generated by hydroelectric resources&amp;quot;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;I&amp;#39;ve been in since before it listed on OTC, first at £0.30 on LSE after finding it here and have averaged up on some dips to £0.85 - it&amp;#39;s almost 20% of my portfolio by now. &lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;It&amp;#39;s held steady this past month, even with some btc dips it&amp;#39;s held well. More catalysts in the pipeline include their new facility in Texas and potential NASDAQ listing after earlier this year appointing same firm Riot used for better US stocks exposure. I see this matching if not at least getting half what Riot &amp;amp; Mara by eoy with how much bitcoin has and will be accepted further in the mainstream finance world now.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt; &amp;#32; submitted by &amp;#32; &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.reddit.com/user/TowerTom&quot;&gt; /u/TowerTom &lt;/a&gt; &amp;#32; to &amp;#32; &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.reddit.com/r/pennystocks/&quot;&gt; r/pennystocks &lt;/a&gt; &lt;br/&gt; &lt;span&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.reddit.com/r/pennystocks/comments/mdmmk7/arbkf_arbl_argo_blockchain_to_launch_first/&quot;&gt;[link]&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &amp;#32; &lt;span&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.reddit.com/r/pennystocks/comments/mdmmk7/arbkf_arbl_argo_blockchain_to_launch_first/&quot;&gt;[comments]&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;</content><id>t3_mdmmk7</id><link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/pennystocks/comments/mdmmk7/arbkf_arbl_argo_blockchain_to_launch_first/" /><updated>2021-03-26T11:36:03+00:00</updated><title>$ARBKF £ARB.L - Argo Blockchain to launch first Bitcoin mining pool powered exclusively by clean energy.</title></entry><entry><author><name>/u/flobbley</name><uri>https://www.reddit.com/user/flobbley</uri></author><category term="stocks" label="r/stocks"/><content type="html">&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;I&amp;#39;ve seen a lot of comments along the lines of &amp;quot;tech stocks are down, but they&amp;#39;ll go back up, there&amp;#39;s no reason not to buy them&amp;quot; but that line of thinking is flawed. Of course tech stocks will go back up, but what&amp;#39;s important to your returns is if you think they will rise faster than whatever index you choose to compare them too. Because if they don&amp;#39;t, you could have just bought that index fund, had less risk, less work, and better returns. You should always be thinking about your stock purchases in the context of &amp;quot;Do I think this will beat the index?&amp;quot; &lt;em&gt;not&lt;/em&gt; &amp;quot;Do I think this will go up in the future?&amp;quot;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Edit: this post is not to advocate for index funds, it is to educate about how to measure stocks returns. This is stocks 101, how well a stock has performed is measured in reference to an index, the difference in returns between the two is called Alpha. Honestly if this concept is new to you then you need to do a lot more research before you try to start picking stocks.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt; &amp;#32; submitted by &amp;#32; &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.reddit.com/user/flobbley&quot;&gt; /u/flobbley &lt;/a&gt; &amp;#32; to &amp;#32; &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.reddit.com/r/stocks/&quot;&gt; r/stocks &lt;/a&gt; &lt;br/&gt; &lt;span&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.reddit.com/r/stocks/comments/mdorgy/remember_it_doesnt_matter_how_much_a_stock_goes/&quot;&gt;[link]&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &amp;#32; &lt;span&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.reddit.com/r/stocks/comments/mdorgy/remember_it_doesnt_matter_how_much_a_stock_goes/&quot;&gt;[comments]&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;</content><id>t3_mdorgy</id><link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/stocks/comments/mdorgy/remember_it_doesnt_matter_how_much_a_stock_goes/" /><updated>2021-03-26T13:34:28+00:00</updated><title>Remember, it doesn't matter how much a stock goes up, what matters is how much more it goes up than the index</title></entry><entry><author><name>/u/Juswatchingthis</name><uri>https://www.reddit.com/user/Juswatchingthis</uri></author><category term="pennystocks" label="r/pennystocks"/><content type="html">&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;I worked a bit on it to try and make it better for you guys. No push or unrealistic price targets here !&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&amp;#x200B;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;So as there are a lot of weed stocks out there let me explain to you why I think &lt;strong&gt;$HCANF&lt;/strong&gt; will be more valuable than others.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&amp;#x200B;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Some major information&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&amp;#x200B;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;- founded in 2015 in medford&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;- sold about 8 million grams of oil and concentrates to this day&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;- constantly growing and expanding into different locations in Afrika, Europe, Kanada and the US&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;- head quarters in West Vancouver / Canada&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;- positive EBITDA will be expected in the Q4 2020 numbers&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;- they will expand into the shroom business and will take agreement&amp;#39;s. &lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&amp;#x200B;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;After these very general informations lets get into some more detail.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&amp;#x200B;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;- many investors see 2021 as a huge chance for halo due to the fact that if they can keep increasing their profits this following year will be their turning point&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;- the potential is huge due to the fact that we have a growing market and with ongoing legalization the demanded amounts will become bigger&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;- they survived as a penny stock through hard times and could become profitable the first time in their history&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;- &lt;strong&gt;FINANCIALS for the Q4 of 2020&lt;/strong&gt; which will decide if they continue to rise &lt;strong&gt;will be published on 31st march 2021&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;- there is am option to carry out a reverse split in 2021 to move out of the pennystock price range and attempt to be listed on NASDAQ - no further informations about a date so far&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;- &lt;strong&gt;$HCANF&lt;/strong&gt; is set to become a leading company with an engaged &lt;strong&gt;CEO Kiran Sidhu&lt;/strong&gt;. He has experience with start up companies and developed them from growing, over making oil, till selling it to the costumer&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;- &lt;strong&gt;some prominent support comes from the rapper G-Eazy&lt;/strong&gt;. He will launch his own products by flower shop and will be supplied by Halo Collective. The opening of the Flowershop Store is planed in summer 2021 in the centre of Hollywood&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;- has huge farming spaces, actually the biggest ones in Africa and is shortly before getting a GACP -certification for Bophelo location which will open the door for expansions into Europe and finally the whole world. &lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&amp;#x200B;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;In the following lines I want to show you some of their upcoming projects&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&amp;#x200B;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;- expanding to the UK, USA, EUROPE&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;- opening 3 stores in Hollywood&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;- the CEO gave an interview where he concluded the upcoming projects - for those that are interested in it&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=2BI4Kdc_Fg8&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=2BI4Kdc_Fg8&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt; &amp;#32; submitted by &amp;#32; &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.reddit.com/user/Juswatchingthis&quot;&gt; /u/Juswatchingthis &lt;/a&gt; &amp;#32; to &amp;#32; &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.reddit.com/r/pennystocks/&quot;&gt; r/pennystocks &lt;/a&gt; &lt;br/&gt; &lt;span&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.reddit.com/r/pennystocks/comments/mdpgom/hcanf_halo_collective_hot_stock_imo_2021_following/&quot;&gt;[link]&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &amp;#32; &lt;span&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.reddit.com/r/pennystocks/comments/mdpgom/hcanf_halo_collective_hot_stock_imo_2021_following/&quot;&gt;[comments]&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;</content><id>t3_mdpgom</id><link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/pennystocks/comments/mdpgom/hcanf_halo_collective_hot_stock_imo_2021_following/" /><updated>2021-03-26T14:08:46+00:00</updated><title>$HCANF -Halo Collective - Hot Stock imo 2021 following</title></entry><entry><author><name>/u/Ex_President35</name><uri>https://www.reddit.com/user/Ex_President35</uri></author><category term="wallstreetbets2" label="r/wallstreetbets2"/><content type="html">&amp;#32; submitted by &amp;#32; &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.reddit.com/user/Ex_President35&quot;&gt; /u/Ex_President35 &lt;/a&gt; &amp;#32; to &amp;#32; &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.reddit.com/r/wallstreetbets2/&quot;&gt; r/wallstreetbets2 &lt;/a&gt; &lt;br/&gt; &lt;span&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://v.redd.it/3ocz77ytxap61&quot;&gt;[link]&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &amp;#32; &lt;span&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.reddit.com/r/wallstreetbets2/comments/mdhymx/whats_good_video_editor_amc_apes/&quot;&gt;[comments]&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;</content><id>t3_mdhymx</id><link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/wallstreetbets2/comments/mdhymx/whats_good_video_editor_amc_apes/" /><updated>2021-03-26T05:58:57+00:00</updated><title>What’s good video editor $AMC APES?</title></entry><entry><author><name>/u/13ry4n</name><uri>https://www.reddit.com/user/13ry4n</uri></author><category term="pennystocks" label="r/pennystocks"/><content type="html">&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Released yesterday&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.globenewswire.com/news-release/2021/03/25/2199442/0/en/Ozop-Energy-OZSC-Develops-the-Neo-Grids-Supply-Chain.html&quot;&gt;https://www.globenewswire.com/news-release/2021/03/25/2199442/0/en/Ozop-Energy-OZSC-Develops-the-Neo-Grids-Supply-Chain.html&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&amp;quot;The exponential growth that the energy production industry is starting to experience is only part of the solution to meeting the needs of the US energy using population. Ozop has positioned itself to supply these markets whether on grid, micro grids, and delayed distribution models. For this model, we will be executing the first step of meeting orders of &lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;$1 million per month&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;, FOB East Coast, with direct drop shipments to the developer’s actual sites. We expect the container ships arriving every 3-5 weeks providing the &lt;em&gt;first&lt;/em&gt; step to being operationally neutral.&amp;quot;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;That&amp;#39;s right, you read that right, &lt;strong&gt;$1 million per month&lt;/strong&gt;.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Also release a few days ago, March 22 2021, the hiring of &lt;strong&gt;Dr. Martello&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://deltadiligence.com/dr-steven-a-martello/&quot;&gt;http://deltadiligence.com/dr-steven-a-martello/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.globenewswire.com/news-release/2021/03/22/2197128/0/en/OZSC-Ozop-Energy-Systems-Announces-New-Corporate-Advisor.html&quot;&gt;https://www.globenewswire.com/news-release/2021/03/22/2197128/0/en/OZSC-Ozop-Energy-Systems-Announces-New-Corporate-Advisor.html&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;M&amp;amp;A. Dr Martello was co-founder and Director of the International Commodity Exchange (ICE) in Moscow, Russia, Chancellor of the International Management Institute, co- founder and CEO/ Chairman of the Nasdaq listed company Alcohol Sensors International, various mortgage and private equity banking operations, and currently as Managing Director and Chairman, of Delta Strategic Solutions and Delta Diligence.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;The entire OTC has been shit on by manipulation and it&amp;#39;s been horrid but a great time to buy in or average down if you bought high.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;If you would like more info, feel free to join the discord channel which is &lt;em&gt;located at the bottom of the PRs&lt;/em&gt;.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;I do hold shares in this company (85% of my portfolio) &amp;amp; have been buying the dips whenever I have some extra cash on hand.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt; &amp;#32; submitted by &amp;#32; &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.reddit.com/user/13ry4n&quot;&gt; /u/13ry4n &lt;/a&gt; &amp;#32; to &amp;#32; &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.reddit.com/r/pennystocks/&quot;&gt; r/pennystocks &lt;/a&gt; &lt;br/&gt; &lt;span&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.reddit.com/r/pennystocks/comments/mdq1jt/ozop_energy_solutions_develops_the_neo_grids/&quot;&gt;[link]&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &amp;#32; &lt;span&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.reddit.com/r/pennystocks/comments/mdq1jt/ozop_energy_solutions_develops_the_neo_grids/&quot;&gt;[comments]&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;</content><id>t3_mdq1jt</id><link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/pennystocks/comments/mdq1jt/ozop_energy_solutions_develops_the_neo_grids/" /><updated>2021-03-26T14:36:53+00:00</updated><title>$OZOP Energy Solutions Develops the Neo Grids Supply + New Corporate Advisor</title></entry><entry><author><name>/u/WeenisWrinkle</name><uri>https://www.reddit.com/user/WeenisWrinkle</uri></author><category term="investing" label="r/investing"/><content type="html">&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.reuters.com/article/ousivMolt/idUSKBN2BH1TQ&quot;&gt;https://www.reuters.com/article/ousivMolt/idUSKBN2BH1TQ&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;The number of Americans filing new claims for unemployment benefits dropped to a one-year low last week, providing a powerful boost to an economy on the verge of stronger growth as the public health situation improves and temperatures rise.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;But the labor market is not out of the woods yet, with the weekly jobless claims report from the Labor Department on Thursday showing a staggering 18.953 million people were still receiving unemployment checks in early March. It will likely take years for a full recovery from the pandemic’s scarring.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Initial claims for state unemployment benefits tumbled 97,000 to a seasonally adjusted 684,000 for the week ended March 20, the lowest since mid-March. Data for the prior week was revised to show 11,000 more applications received than previously reported. Economists polled by Reuters had forecast 730,000 applications for the latest week.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt; &amp;#32; submitted by &amp;#32; &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.reddit.com/user/WeenisWrinkle&quot;&gt; /u/WeenisWrinkle &lt;/a&gt; &amp;#32; to &amp;#32; &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.reddit.com/r/investing/&quot;&gt; r/investing &lt;/a&gt; &lt;br/&gt; &lt;span&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.reddit.com/r/investing/comments/md3d5a/us_weekly_jobless_claims_hit_oneyear_low_in_boost/&quot;&gt;[link]&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &amp;#32; &lt;span&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.reddit.com/r/investing/comments/md3d5a/us_weekly_jobless_claims_hit_oneyear_low_in_boost/&quot;&gt;[comments]&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;</content><id>t3_md3d5a</id><link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/investing/comments/md3d5a/us_weekly_jobless_claims_hit_oneyear_low_in_boost/" /><updated>2021-03-25T17:17:09+00:00</updated><title>U.S. weekly jobless claims hit one-year low in boost to economic outlook $VMNT</title></entry><entry><author><name>/u/NEOstockhacker</name><uri>https://www.reddit.com/user/NEOstockhacker</uri></author><category term="pennystocks" label="r/pennystocks"/><content type="html">&lt;table&gt; &lt;tr&gt;&lt;td&gt; &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.reddit.com/r/pennystocks/comments/mdojop/vmnt_qb_new_filings_institutional_investors_gets/&quot;&gt; &lt;img src=&quot;https://b.thumbs.redditmedia.com/YN3Sc1fkSiU51MeATJNdGb7wsDo0MNOy_WTEqqJxubo.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;$VMNT QB NEW FILINGS | Institutional Investors Gets Green Light #Defi #Fintech #StableCoin&quot; title=&quot; $VMNT QB NEW FILINGS | Institutional Investors Gets Green Light #Defi #Fintech #StableCoin&quot; /&gt; &lt;/a&gt; &lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt; &lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;In a tweet 2 days ago CEO, Tan Tran said&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&amp;quot;BTW, institutional investors have been waiting for Vemanti $VMNT to finish its 2020 financial audit. We got it done yesterday!&amp;quot;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;The next day OTCQB Certification and 12/31/2020 Annual report gets published, don&amp;#39;t ever doubt this man. &lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&amp;#x200B;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://preview.redd.it/vkpzycvehdp61.png?width=1110&amp;amp;format=png&amp;amp;auto=webp&amp;amp;s=47d67b6c3a54b0f23165e78afb7abcef3df65dc7&quot;&gt;OTCQB Certification &lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&amp;#x200B;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://preview.redd.it/dbwq9uqghdp61.png?width=1127&amp;amp;format=png&amp;amp;auto=webp&amp;amp;s=897777169e68ff5c89d826ab249204bb9a4f560c&quot;&gt;12/31/2020 Annual report&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&amp;#x200B;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;CEO also kept his word that RJI international CAPs will be doing the auditing.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;RJI CPAs Recognized as one of America’s Top Tax and Accounting Firms by Forbes.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&amp;#x200B;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Most new traders wouldn&amp;#39;t understand the value of having a credible auditor like RJI CPAs means. To put everything into perspective in regards to the auditor, this just adds another stamp of legitimacy and quality. We&amp;#39;re dealing with institutional investors now. Quality is key.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&amp;#x200B;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://preview.redd.it/dog7g4f7idp61.png?width=1883&amp;amp;format=png&amp;amp;auto=webp&amp;amp;s=7e0245d121c873d5f31effae307f9d399fe938ca&quot;&gt;RJI CAPs&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt; &amp;#32; submitted by &amp;#32; &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.reddit.com/user/NEOstockhacker&quot;&gt; /u/NEOstockhacker &lt;/a&gt; &amp;#32; to &amp;#32; &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.reddit.com/r/pennystocks/&quot;&gt; r/pennystocks &lt;/a&gt; &lt;br/&gt; &lt;span&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.reddit.com/r/pennystocks/comments/mdojop/vmnt_qb_new_filings_institutional_investors_gets/&quot;&gt;[link]&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &amp;#32; &lt;span&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.reddit.com/r/pennystocks/comments/mdojop/vmnt_qb_new_filings_institutional_investors_gets/&quot;&gt;[comments]&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;&lt;/table&gt;</content><id>t3_mdojop</id><media:thumbnail url="https://b.thumbs.redditmedia.com/YN3Sc1fkSiU51MeATJNdGb7wsDo0MNOy_WTEqqJxubo.jpg" /><link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/pennystocks/comments/mdojop/vmnt_qb_new_filings_institutional_investors_gets/" /><updated>2021-03-26T13:23:09+00:00</updated><title>$VMNT QB NEW FILINGS | Institutional Investors Gets Green Light #Defi #Fintech #StableCoin</title></entry><entry><author><name>/u/Printer84</name><uri>https://www.reddit.com/user/Printer84</uri></author><category term="pennystocks" label="r/pennystocks"/><content type="html">&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://finance.yahoo.com/news/clickstreams-heypal-tm-app-surpassed-123000387.html&quot;&gt;https://finance.yahoo.com/news/clickstreams-heypal-tm-app-surpassed-123000387.html&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;March 26, 2021&lt;/strong&gt; / ClickStream Corp. (OTC PINK:CLIS) a technology company focused on developing apps and digital platforms that disrupt conventional industries announces its subsidiary Nebula Software Corp.&amp;#39;s HeyPal™ app received a total of over 400,000 messages, 100,000 translations, 20,000 likes between almost 10,000 members since the app was beta-released on Monday, February 8th in a select group of countries as part of the beta soft launch program. HeyPal™ is currently live in 15 countries, including: Australia, Taiwan, Spain, Ireland, Switzerland, Morocco, Ukraine, Turkey, Colombia, Israel, United Kingdom, Brazil, Germany, Italy &amp;amp; South Korea.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;HeyPal™&lt;/strong&gt;, by way of ClickStream subsidiary Nebula Software Corp., is a language learning app that focuses on &amp;quot;language exchanging&amp;quot; between users around the world.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Nifter™&lt;/strong&gt;, by way of ClickStream subsidiary Rebel Blockchain Inc., is a music NFT marketplace that allows artists to create, sell and discover unique music and sound NFTs on the Nifter™ marketplace. &lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;HeyPal and Nifter are going to keep bringing this stock up!&lt;/p&gt; &lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt; &amp;#32; submitted by &amp;#32; &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.reddit.com/user/Printer84&quot;&gt; /u/Printer84 &lt;/a&gt; &amp;#32; to &amp;#32; &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.reddit.com/r/pennystocks/&quot;&gt; r/pennystocks &lt;/a&gt; &lt;br/&gt; &lt;span&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.reddit.com/r/pennystocks/comments/mdo6qx/clis_heypaltm_app_has_surpassed_expectations_by/&quot;&gt;[link]&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &amp;#32; &lt;span&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.reddit.com/r/pennystocks/comments/mdo6qx/clis_heypaltm_app_has_surpassed_expectations_by/&quot;&gt;[comments]&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;</content><id>t3_mdo6qx</id><link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/pennystocks/comments/mdo6qx/clis_heypaltm_app_has_surpassed_expectations_by/" /><updated>2021-03-26T13:04:57+00:00</updated><title>$CLIS HeyPal(TM) App has Surpassed Expectations by Reaching Over 400,000 Messages, 100,000 translations, 20,000 likes and almost 10,000 Members During the First 6 Weeks of Beta Soft Launch in Initial 15 Countries</title></entry><entry><author><name>/u/Top-Acanthocephala46</name><uri>https://www.reddit.com/user/Top-Acanthocephala46</uri></author><category term="wallstreetbets2" label="r/wallstreetbets2"/><content type="html">&amp;#32; submitted by &amp;#32; &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.reddit.com/user/Top-Acanthocephala46&quot;&gt; /u/Top-Acanthocephala46 &lt;/a&gt; &amp;#32; to &amp;#32; &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.reddit.com/r/wallstreetbets2/&quot;&gt; r/wallstreetbets2 &lt;/a&gt; &lt;br/&gt; &lt;span&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://i.redd.it/5ae4eztfz5p61.jpg&quot;&gt;[link]&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &amp;#32; &lt;span&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.reddit.com/r/wallstreetbets2/comments/mcwsrf/here_we_go_game_on/&quot;&gt;[comments]&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;</content><id>t3_mcwsrf</id><link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/wallstreetbets2/comments/mcwsrf/here_we_go_game_on/" /><updated>2021-03-25T12:12:35+00:00</updated><title>Here we go. $GME on</title></entry><entry><author><name>/u/kayaarr</name><uri>https://www.reddit.com/user/kayaarr</uri></author><category term="stocks" label="r/stocks"/><content type="html">&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Online finance start-up SoFi ($IPOE) is lowering the barrier for amateur investors to buy shares of companies as they go public.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;These IPO shares have historically been set aside for Wall Street’s institutional investors or high-net worth individuals. Retail traders don’t have a way to buy into newly listed companies until those shares begin actually trading on the exchange. By that time, the price has often gapped higher.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;“Main Street will have access to investing in a way they wouldn’t have before,” SoFi CEO Anthony Noto said in a phone interview. “It gives more differentiation, and more access so people can build diversified portfolios.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;SoFi itself will be an underwriter in these deals, meaning it works with companies to determine a share price, buys securities from the issuer then sells them back to certain investors. It’s common for brokerage firms to get a portion of IPO shares in that process. But they don’t typically offer them to the everyday investor. &lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.cnbc.com/2021/03/26/sofi-to-give-amateur-investors-early-access-to-ipos-in-break-from-wall-street-tradition-.html&quot;&gt;Source&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt; &amp;#32; submitted by &amp;#32; &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.reddit.com/user/kayaarr&quot;&gt; /u/kayaarr &lt;/a&gt; &amp;#32; to &amp;#32; &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.reddit.com/r/stocks/&quot;&gt; r/stocks &lt;/a&gt; &lt;br/&gt; &lt;span&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.reddit.com/r/stocks/comments/mdoppt/sofi_to_give_amateur_investors_early_access_to/&quot;&gt;[link]&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &amp;#32; &lt;span&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.reddit.com/r/stocks/comments/mdoppt/sofi_to_give_amateur_investors_early_access_to/&quot;&gt;[comments]&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;</content><id>t3_mdoppt</id><link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/stocks/comments/mdoppt/sofi_to_give_amateur_investors_early_access_to/" /><updated>2021-03-26T13:31:56+00:00</updated><title>SoFi to give amateur investors early access to IPOs in break from Wall Street tradition</title></entry><entry><author><name>/u/ReasonableWindow7383</name><uri>https://www.reddit.com/user/ReasonableWindow7383</uri></author><category term="pennystocks" label="r/pennystocks"/><content type="html">&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;h1&gt;Analyzing $EEENF &amp;#39;s Path before imminent news.&lt;/h1&gt; &lt;p&gt;📷&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Today started off rather rough, with an opening less ideal than we all expected. A classic dip around 11 emerged, stumping many. This can be easily justified by major funds shorting the stock in conjunction with buying it at that lower dip. People panic selling didn&amp;#39;t help either. However, FOMO helped us push through all of this downtrading pressure, and in the end we held a rally as shorts covered and funds bought. The big question really is tomorrow, and the price we will see for the stock. There are many factors. 1. Social media presence and more importantly &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.reddit.com/r/pennystocks/&quot;&gt;r/pennystocks&lt;/a&gt; presence and knowing about this ticker. The best way to win big on great news is to have a lot of people find out. Tomorrow will likely open with a small dip from selling and shorting, followed by retail investors scooping up shares in speculation. Breaking .030 sometime during the day is almost a definite, as we are flying through every resistance point and approaching a blue sky breakout, similar to MDMP pre announcement. Next is the news. Naturally, I&amp;#39;m a pessimist. However, I&amp;#39;m optimistic on EEENF.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;ol&gt; &lt;li&gt;9 out of 10 Wells located north of Merlin-1 have found viable industrial grade oil.&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;David Wall repeating multiple times in interviews that his goal is to strike oil and sell his company to the highest bidder.&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;ELKO receiving shares for their labor. Some may think of this as a spur of the moment decision, but it isn&amp;#39;t. They were informed of the project before December, at a price lower than the 6.5 million range they are being payed now. The increased price is from delays and confirmation to start drilling.&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;Mud logging, a process of estimating with oil in the area, apparently should be known by Sunday night. A bad result in the beginning oil field layers may have resulted in an early announcement declaring absence of oil.&lt;/li&gt; &lt;/ol&gt; &lt;p&gt;In the end, hold if you got in below .025 range, or buy if you don&amp;#39;t have a position yet. My price target is .30 cents based upon O/S and hype.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt; &amp;#32; submitted by &amp;#32; &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.reddit.com/user/ReasonableWindow7383&quot;&gt; /u/ReasonableWindow7383 &lt;/a&gt; &amp;#32; to &amp;#32; &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.reddit.com/r/pennystocks/&quot;&gt; r/pennystocks &lt;/a&gt; &lt;br/&gt; &lt;span&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.reddit.com/r/pennystocks/comments/md7o1c/eeenf_read_this/&quot;&gt;[link]&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &amp;#32; &lt;span&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.reddit.com/r/pennystocks/comments/md7o1c/eeenf_read_this/&quot;&gt;[comments]&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;</content><id>t3_md7o1c</id><link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/pennystocks/comments/md7o1c/eeenf_read_this/" /><updated>2021-03-25T20:31:11+00:00</updated><title>$EEENF READ THIS</title></entry><entry><author><name>/u/FckMyStudentLoans</name><uri>https://www.reddit.com/user/FckMyStudentLoans</uri></author><category term="pennystocks" label="r/pennystocks"/><content type="html">&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://finance.yahoo.com/news/global-tech-industries-group-inc-143000208.html&quot;&gt;https://finance.yahoo.com/news/global-tech-industries-group-inc-143000208.html&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt; &amp;#32; submitted by &amp;#32; &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.reddit.com/user/FckMyStudentLoans&quot;&gt; /u/FckMyStudentLoans &lt;/a&gt; &amp;#32; to &amp;#32; &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.reddit.com/r/pennystocks/&quot;&gt; r/pennystocks &lt;/a&gt; &lt;br/&gt; &lt;span&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.reddit.com/r/pennystocks/comments/mdq9j6/gtii_global_tech_industries_group_nft_acquisition/&quot;&gt;[link]&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &amp;#32; &lt;span&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.reddit.com/r/pennystocks/comments/mdq9j6/gtii_global_tech_industries_group_nft_acquisition/&quot;&gt;[comments]&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;</content><id>t3_mdq9j6</id><link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/pennystocks/comments/mdq9j6/gtii_global_tech_industries_group_nft_acquisition/" /><updated>2021-03-26T14:47:58+00:00</updated><title>$GTII - Global Tech Industries Group NFT Acquisition PR Today - Up 25%</title></entry><entry><author><name>/u/wetdirtkurt</name><uri>https://www.reddit.com/user/wetdirtkurt</uri></author><category term="pennystocks" label="r/pennystocks"/><content type="html">&lt;table&gt; &lt;tr&gt;&lt;td&gt; &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.reddit.com/r/pennystocks/comments/mdexsk/eeenf_share_price_valuation_model_low_range/&quot;&gt; &lt;img src=&quot;https://b.thumbs.redditmedia.com/5e182t7HIlMaPFdCecboaCJq1NChreDDb7KjZy3aG3I.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;$EEENF Share Price Valuation Model | Low Range Estimate increase of 1700% in Current Share Price Equaling $0.49 Per Share| Average Range Estimate Increase in Current Share Price of 3600% Equaling $1.05 Per Share | 🚀🚀🚀&quot; title=&quot;$EEENF Share Price Valuation Model | Low Range Estimate increase of 1700% in Current Share Price Equaling $0.49 Per Share| Average Range Estimate Increase in Current Share Price of 3600% Equaling $1.05 Per Share | 🚀🚀🚀&quot; /&gt; &lt;/a&gt; &lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt; &lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;I posted this on the &lt;a href=&quot;/r/eeenf&quot;&gt;/r/eeenf&lt;/a&gt; but didn&amp;#39;t get much feedback or rocket emojis so I am reposting here with some additional commentary to provide what is going on in my model.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Using the estimated output of Merlin-1 of 645M Barrels of Oil (+ or - 10% to give a buffer for the estimate and to establish a high and low range for share price), the current price of a barrel of oil, the 100 day moving average on a barrel of oil (an increase of $20.62 at current price), the estimated break-even price of drilling for a single barrel of oil in Alaska of $40, the current market capitalization as of today&amp;#39;s close (according to Yahoo Finance $316M), the company&amp;#39;s own December 31, 2020 Financial Statements to gather cash and debt balances, current share price ($.0286), and some benchmark industry revenue multiples for oil - I made four separate valuation matrixes using three different methodologies to estimate future share price if Merlin-1 is successful. Two of them (the two rightmost) are the same method, just different sources for the multiples.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;The valuation methodologies are generally accepted as standard in finance. Each calculation is referenced between each data point in blue (A, B, C...etc). Each cell that is highlighted a color are related to other cells of the same color. At the bottom, you get the ranges for each methodology using the estimated output plus or minus the 10% buffer and the current and expected future price of oil.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Finally, I highlight the absolute highest and lowest estimate of each methodology as well as the overall average by each methodology. I do this again, but use only the highest and lowest estimate of all the methodologies and then average all of the estimates that are shown arriving us at $1.05 per share.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Here are the references I used, although not all of them.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;R1 -&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.spglobal.com/marketintelligence/en/news-insights/latest-news-headlines/half-of-producing-shale-oil-wells-are-profitable-at-40-bbl-analyst-says-60035427&quot;&gt;https://www.spglobal.com/marketintelligence/en/news-insights/latest-news-headlines/half-of-producing-shale-oil-wells-are-profitable-at-40-bbl-analyst-says-60035427&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;R2/R3 -&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.equidam.com/ebitda-multiples-trbc-industries/&quot;&gt;https://www.equidam.com/ebitda-multiples-trbc-industries/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;R4 -&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href=&quot;http://pages.stern.nyu.edu/%7Eadamodar/New_Home_Page/datafile/vebitda.html&quot;&gt;http://pages.stern.nyu.edu/~adamodar/New_Home_Page/datafile/vebitda.html&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;R5 -&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.eval.tech/valuation-multiples-by-industry&quot;&gt;https://www.eval.tech/valuation-multiples-by-industry&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Here is the link to the google sheet if you want to poke around a little bit. Commenting is turned on if you want to give feedback. I will change anything I agree with. &lt;a href=&quot;https://docs.google.com/spreadsheets/d/1obQVjCeDD3WmyuNZEC4a_FZK3kEh_85m3JkG6lLqXes/edit?usp=sharing&quot;&gt;https://docs.google.com/spreadsheets/d/1obQVjCeDD3WmyuNZEC4a_FZK3kEh_85m3JkG6lLqXes/edit?usp=sharing&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;DISCLAIMER: this is not financial advice. I am not a financial adviser. I am just some fucking guy.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://preview.redd.it/mhzkpdjzcap61.png?width=1462&amp;amp;format=png&amp;amp;auto=webp&amp;amp;s=f4103e7176d40b4f4d70d0a2b2ddd6319b49fc2e&quot;&gt;https://preview.redd.it/mhzkpdjzcap61.png?width=1462&amp;amp;format=png&amp;amp;auto=webp&amp;amp;s=f4103e7176d40b4f4d70d0a2b2ddd6319b49fc2e&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt; &amp;#32; submitted by &amp;#32; &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.reddit.com/user/wetdirtkurt&quot;&gt; /u/wetdirtkurt &lt;/a&gt; &amp;#32; to &amp;#32; &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.reddit.com/r/pennystocks/&quot;&gt; r/pennystocks &lt;/a&gt; &lt;br/&gt; &lt;span&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.reddit.com/r/pennystocks/comments/mdexsk/eeenf_share_price_valuation_model_low_range/&quot;&gt;[link]&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &amp;#32; &lt;span&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.reddit.com/r/pennystocks/comments/mdexsk/eeenf_share_price_valuation_model_low_range/&quot;&gt;[comments]&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;&lt;/table&gt;</content><id>t3_mdexsk</id><media:thumbnail url="https://b.thumbs.redditmedia.com/5e182t7HIlMaPFdCecboaCJq1NChreDDb7KjZy3aG3I.jpg" /><media:preview url="https://external-preview.redd.it/mM5WAvgi9ejJ7ZdiGnRbz06VzXQnQ0sOdFpluH-fqOY.jpg?width=108&amp;crop=smart&amp;auto=webp&amp;s=f9ce8bd49f4114abe1a64a1c96d969287e409bc3" width="108" height="80" /><link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/pennystocks/comments/mdexsk/eeenf_share_price_valuation_model_low_range/" /><updated>2021-03-26T02:44:10+00:00</updated><title>$EEENF Share Price Valuation Model | Low Range Estimate increase of 1700% in Current Share Price Equaling $0.49 Per Share| Average Range Estimate Increase in Current Share Price of 3600% Equaling $1.05 Per Share</title></entry></feed>